字幕译制--贝支子--
快点，我们去找这家伙。 我知道他在这里的某个地方。
Come on, let's find this guy. I know he's here somewhere.
来吧，找他。继续走。 我们会找到他的。我知道在这里。
Come on, look for him. Just keep going. We're gonna find him. I know it's here.
-在那里！ -在右边。
- There! - Over to the right.
看到那边了吗？看到什么了吗？
See over there? See anything?
-就这样。 -就在那儿！
- That's it. - There it is!
就这样。好吧！
That's it. All right!
-就这样。 -让我们把这个混蛋撕开！
- This is it. - Let's rip this sucker open!
我得去看看主角。
Gotta get a look at the main man.
耶哈哈！
Yee-haw!
来吧，挖。更深的。
Come on, dig. Deeper.
来吧，挖。来吧，我们挖。 快点，快点。挖掘。
Come on, dig. Come on, let's dig. Come on, faster. Dig.
挖！
Dig!
我们把所有的脏东西都拿开 把它撬开。就这样。
Let's just get all the dirt off and let's pry it open. This is it.
快点！
Come on!
-窥探。 -把它移到这里。
- Pry. - Move it over here.
更努力。来吧。
Harder. Come on.
-加油，尼尔！ -嗯。好了，来了。
- Come on, Neil! - Unh. Okay, here it comes.
不，不。
No. No.
不！
No!
那一定是新来的孩子。
That must be the new kid.
最后一站，大家都出去。
Last stop, everybody out.
汤米？嘿。
Tommy? Hey.
不？美丽的。坐在那里。 我才不管呢。
No? Beautiful. Sit there. I don't give a shit.
嘿。你好吗？
Hey. How you doing?
汤米?贾维斯？嗨，我的 我叫帕姆?罗伯茨。
Tommy Jarvis? Hi, my name is Pam Roberts.
我是助理导演。 很高兴你能来。
I'm the assistant director. I'm glad you're here.
好吧，如果你想拿你的东西， 我带你去见医生，好吗？
Well, if you'd like to grab your things, I'll take you in to meet the doctor, okay?
伟大的。
Great.
谢谢您。
Thank you.
什么时候都行，娃娃。
Anytime, doll.
旅途如何？
How was the ride?
快点，汤米。
Come on, Tommy.
你还好吧？
You okay?
进来吧。
Come in.
你好。
Hi.
嗨，汤米。我是马修?莱特。 欢迎来到松树园。请坐。
Hi, Tommy. I'm Matthew Letter. Welcome to Pinehurst. Have a seat.
坐下，孩子。
Sit down, son.
呃，我要做的是告诉你 你有点喜欢松树。。。
Uh, what I'm gonna do is tell you a little about Pinehurst...
然后我们就让你安顿下来 你的房间。听起来怎么样？
and then we'll let you get settled in your room. How does that sound?
汤米？
Tommy?
听起来怎么样？
How does that sound?
当然。
Sure.
好吧。关于松树。。。
All right. About Pinehurst...
你会发现我们很不一样 来自国家机构。
you'll find we're very different from the state institution.
呃，我们没有 这里的守卫。。。
Uh, we don't have any guards here...
没人会告诉你 能做或不能做的事。
nobody's gonna tell you what you can do or what you can't do.
-基本上，你是你自己的老板。 -这是个荣誉制度，汤米。
- Basically, you're your own boss. - It's an honor system, Tommy.
你到底是什么 在这里做，汤米。。。
What you're really doing here, Tommy...
准备重新进入 开始新的生活。
is preparing yourself to reenter society and start a new life.
所以，帕姆，你想指点汤米 去他的房间然后让他开始？
So, Pam, you wanna point Tommy toward his room and get him started?
当然。可以？好吧，你通过 厨房，楼上。。。
Sure. Okay? All right, you go through the kitchen, up the stairs...
这是你的第一扇门 左边，好吗？一会儿见。
and it's the first door on your left, okay? I'll see you in a bit.
那么，你觉得呢？
So, what do you think?
-这孩子真会说话。 -嘿。
- The kid's a real talker. - Heh.
我注意到了。他们怎么诊断的？
I noticed. How'd they diagnose it?
呃，“12岁时严重创伤。
Uh, "Severe trauma at age 12.
残忍的自卫谋杀 一个精神变态的杀手。”
Brutal self-defense murder of a psychopathic killer."
孩子，他们给了他 每次治疗。。。
Boy, they've given him every treatment...
他们能想到的每一种治疗方法。
every therapy they can think of.
奇怪的是他的头脑没有被炸， 他们给他的所有毒品。
It's a wonder his mind isn't fried, with all the drugs they've given him.
你害怕蜘蛛？ 你害怕橡胶蜘蛛？
You scared of spiders? You scared of rubber spiders?
你害怕绳子上的橡胶蜘蛛？ 伙计，你真是个胆小鬼。
You scared of rubber spiders on strings? Man, you are one scared cat.
我从哪里来，你就知道 什么都不怕。
Where I come from, you learn to be scared of nothing.
他们叫我鲁莽的雷吉。 没有蜘蛛会吓到我。
They call me Reggie the Reckless. No spider would scare me.
哟，伙计！
Yo, man!
不要。
Don't.
你不必得到所有 它扭曲变形了。
You don't have to get all twisted out of shape about it.
我是说，你表现得像 这些东西什么的。
I mean, you act like you made these things or something.
是的。
I did.
真的。
Solid.
所以你是新来的疯子，嗯？
So you're the new nut, huh?
-他们就是这么叫我们的吗？ -我们？我不是你们中的一员，伙计。
- Is that what they call us? - Us? I ain't one of you, man.
我只是来拜访。我的 爷爷在这里工作。
I'm just visiting. My granddaddy works here.
哦，得分开了。抓住你 稍后。有行动。
Oh, gotta split. Catch you later. There's action.
乔伊，来吧。快点。 哦，天哪！喔！
Joey, come on. Hurry up. Oh, my God! Whoo!
嘿，你们两个。乔伊，来吧。
Hey, you guys. Joey, come on.
停下，来吧。不要！
Stop, come on. Don't!
-快点，停下！ -呆在这里。
- Come on, stop! - Stay right here.
-嘿，马特。怎么样？ -好吧，警长。怎么了？
- Hey, Matt. How's it going? - All right, sheriff. What's up?
好吧，马特，你知道的， 就像我们说的。
Well, Matt, you know, it's like we talked about.
你有一些邻居不是 你在这里过得太开心了。
You got some neighbors who aren't too happy about your place here.
现在，我知道你是什么了 努力做到，我尊重它，马特，我做到了。
Now, I certainly know what it is you're trying to do, and I respect it, Matt, I do.
但是，你看，我们发现了 你的孩子又在哈伯德家了。
But, well, you see we found a couple of your kids on the Hubbard place again.
-副手！ -是的，先生。
- Deputy! - Yes, sir.
-把他们带出来。 -是的，先生。
- Bring them out. - Yes, sir.
大家都出去。
Everybody out.
别胡闹了。 被治安官逮捕。
Cut out the fooling around. Fall in by the sheriff.
-是的，先生。 -快走，聪明人。
- Yes, sir. - Just get moving, wise guy.
我们在 哈伯德森林。
We found them in the Hubbards' woods.
他们在搞砸 他们的头掉下来，马特。
They were screwing their heads off, Matt.
现在，我觉得我们都很幸运 时间，因为埃塞尔没看见他们。
Now, I think we're all pretty lucky this time, because Ethel didn't see them.
我会处理的，警长。
I'll take care of it, sheriff.
我来谈谈。 你保持安静。
I'm gonna do the talking. You keep quiet.
早上好，埃塞尔。
Morning, Ethel.
-天啊，你今天看起来真可爱。 -胡说！
- My, don't you look lovely today. - Horseshit!
现在，警长，你最好 听我说，好好听我说。
Now, sheriff, you better hear me and hear me good.
我要把这个疯子箱子关了。
I want this loony bin closed down.
听到了吗，伙计？现在，这些 孩子们除了麻烦什么都不是！
Do you hear me, fella? Now, these kids ain't nothing but trouble!
他们不尊重别人 他们都疯了！
They don't respect others' property and they're all crazy!
-你告诉他们，妈！哈，哈。 -埃塞尔，这些孩子没有。。。
- You tell them, Ma! Ha, ha. - Ethel, these kids weren't doing...
做什么？做什么？
Doing? Doing?
你以为我不知道那些 两个变态在我院子里干什么？
You think I don't know what those two perverts were doing in my yard?
-像你说的那样说吧，妈！ -你他妈的能闭嘴吗？
- Say it like you mean it, Ma! - Would you shut the fuck up?
现在，我要告诉你们所有人：
Now, I'm gonna tell all of you:
你记下我的话 混蛋靠近我的农场。。。
You mark my words, the next little bastard comes near my farm...
我要炸了你 头脑清醒。听到了吗？
I'm gonna blow your fucking brains out. You hear me?
别靠近我， 警长。我警告过你。
Don't you come near me, sheriff. I've warned you.
我身上有炸弹。我向你发誓！
I got a bomb on me. I swear to you!
你朝我走一步， 我要把我们都炸了。
You make one move toward me, I'm gonna blow us all up.
启动引擎，小家伙。 就这样。我的最后一句话。
Start the engines, Junior. That's it. My final words.
好的，各位。来吧， 走吧。派对结束了。
Okay, people. Come on, let's go. Party's over.
-来吧，伙计们。 -我们最好回去。
- Come on, you guys. - We better go back inside.
-她真的很了不起，不是吗？ -上帝啊。
- She's really something, ain't she? - Jesus.
说真的，马特，我会加倍努力 让你的孩子远离她的财产。
Seriously, Matt, I'd make an extra effort to keep your kids off her property.
-我会的。 -听着，顺便说一句。。。
- I will. - Now, listen, by the way...
我知道你有 今天是贾维斯的孩子。
I understand you got the Jarvis kid today.
-是的，他刚到。 -然后呢？
- Yeah, he arrived a little while ago. - And?
-那又怎样？ -他长什么样？
- And what? - Well, what's he like?
他和其他孩子一样。他只是，呃。。。 他经历了很多，仅此而已。
He's like any other kid. He's just, uh... He's been through a lot, that's all.
-是的。好吧，祝他好运，伙计。 -非常感谢，警长。
- Yeah. Well, good luck with him, pal. - Thanks a lot, sheriff.
-嗨，姑娘们。 -嗨，乔伊。
- Hi, girls. - Hi, Joey.
-嗨，维奥莱特。 -嗯？
- Hi, Violet. - Huh?
-嗨！ -是的。
- Hi! - Yeah.
-你在干什么？ -洗衣服，乔伊。
- What are you doing? - Doing laundry, Joey.
我能帮忙吗？我真的非常 擅长洗衣服。
Can I help? I'm really very good at doing laundry.
马特从不把它分配给 我，我不知道为什么。
Matt never assigns it to me, I don't know why.
听着，乔伊，我们真的必须 把这件事做完，好吗？
Look, Joey, we really have to get this thing finished, okay?
所以我是来帮你的。
So I'm here to help you.
你可以相信我， 罗布。你也是，维。
You can count on me, Rob. You too, Vi.
想要一块巧克力吗？在这里， 你想要吗？我给你一半。。。
Want a chocolate bar? Here, you want it? I'll give you half...
-但我以后需要一半。 -滚开！
- but I need half for later. - Piss off!
噢，请让我来帮你。 真的没问题。。。
Oh, please let me help you. It's really no problem...
-乔伊！你能离开这里吗？ -操！
- Joey! Will you just get out of here? - Fuck!
对不起，你们两个。真正地， 我可以洗衣服。但是。。。
I'm sorry, you two. Really, I can do laundry great. But...
如果是这样的话 你感觉，忘记它。
well, if that's how you feel, forget it.
我去帮别人 而不是别的。待会儿见。
I'll just go help somebody else instead. I'll see you later.
我真不敢相信。
I can't believe this.
听着，如果你改变主意， 我马上就来，好吗？
Listen, if you change your mind, I'll be right around, okay?
-乔伊！ -乔伊。
- Joey! - Joey.
天哪，真是个失败者。
Jesus, what a loser.
看这张纸。我没有 去洗吧。你洗吧。
Look at this sheet. I'm not gonna wash it. You wash it.
-嗨，维克！ -迷路吧。
- Hi, Vic! - Get lost.
别这样，别这样。我是 今天帮你搬木头。
Come on, don't be like that. I'm gonna help you with the wood today.
不管怎样，呃，我有两个 巧克力棒，明白吗？
And anyway, uh, I got two chocolate bars, see?
-别告诉女孩们。 -天啊，真是个混蛋。
- Don't tell the girls. - Jeez, what an asshole.
你知道吗，维克，在我来之前， 我从没做过什么。。。
You know, Vic, before I came here, I never had anything to do...
我是个孤儿。
me being an orphan and all.
人们总是取笑我 关于坐着。。。
People always teased me about sitting around...
像猪之类的。
like some kind of pig or something.
但这里不一样。我可以帮忙 其他人和做很多事情。
But here it's different. I can help others and do a lot of things.
你知道吗？ 我真的很喜欢这里。
You know something? I really love it here.
我讨厌它。
I hate it.
你知道，嗯，说实话 你，我以前从没切过木头。。。
You know, um, to be perfectly honest with you, I never really chopped wood before...
但看起来确实很有趣。
but it certainly looks like fun.
别管我！
Leave me alone!
给你，维克。想吃一口吗？
Here, Vic. Want a bite?
在这里。我就把它放在这里。。。
Here. I'll just put it over here...
以后，当你 饿了，你可以吃了。
and later on, when you're hungry, you can have it.
如果你是这么想的， 算了吧，维克。算了吧！
Well, if that's the way you feel, forget it, Vic. Just forget it!
但我觉得你 太过分了。
But I think you're really out of line.
是的，我们手上有凶杀案。 看看你有什么法登。
Yeah, we got a homicide on our hands. See what you got on a Faden.
维克多法登。 谢谢，哈里。
Victor J. Faden. F-A-D-E-N. Thanks, Harry.
-嘘。没关系。 -为什么？
- Shh. It's Okay. - Why?
我们应该通知谁吗？
Is there someone we should notify?
据我所知 没有直系亲属。
As far as I know, there's no immediate family.
母亲在生孩子的时候死了。。。
Mother died while giving birth...
我不知道到底发生了什么事 父亲。我想是在什么地方起飞的。
I don't know what the hell happened to the father. Took off somewhere, I guess.
这孩子是从 直到他来到这里。
This kid got shuffled around from home to home till he came here.
-他是个好孩子。 -我知道，马特。
- He was a good kid. - I know, Matt.
那么，我们这里有什么？
So, what do we got here?
哦，天哪！
Oh, God!
没关系。
It's all right.
一群娘娘腔。
Bunch of pussies.
来吧，罗伊。把你的手弄脏。
Come on, Roy. Get your hands dirty.
我告诉你，皮特，这是 瞎扯！真糟糕！
I'm telling you, Pete, this is bullshit! This really sucks!
想做就做。修好它，伙计！那些 女人不会等一整晚的。
Just do it. Fix it, man! Those cunts aren't gonna wait all night.
哦，操！真是一团糟。
Oh, fuck! This is a mess.
不可能，我拒绝这样做。
No way, I refuse to do this.
你才是那个不停做爱的人 带着这个东西。。。
You're the one who keeps fucking around with this thing...
所以放开你的屁股去修好它！
so get off your ass and you fix it!
你明白吗？
You understand?
皮特！
Pete!
操死
Fuck.
-你是个混蛋！ -哦，怎么了，文尼？
- You are an asshole! - Aw, what's the matter, Vinnie?
你害怕黑暗？
You scared of the dark?
你们都被那个吓坏了 在疯人院杀人？
You all creeped out by that murder at the nuthouse?
哦，是的，当然。听着，只要 我担心，那些疯子。。。
Oh, yeah, sure. Look, as far as I'm concerned, all those loonies...
应该一个一个的被杀。 你现在能试试吗？
should be killed off one by one. Can you try it now?
天哪，伙计！你不能做什么吗？ 别胡闹了！
Jesus, man! Can't you do anything? Stop screwing around!
在我之前把这件事做完 回去。我要吃点屎。
Get this done by the time I get back. I gotta take a crap.
-该死，我的屁股！ -干吧，伙计！我是认真的。
- Crap, my ass! - Just do it, man! I mean it.
他妈的混蛋！
Fucking asshole!
哦，你这个小混蛋。
Oh, you little fuck.
你在干什么，笨蛋？
What are you doing, douche bag?
已经够了。你可以停下来。
Enough already. You can stop.
你能把它剪掉吗？
Would you cut it out?
皮特！
Pete!
好吧，要么你有车 开始否则你就死定了。
All right, either you got the car started or you're a dead man.
这不是开始，伙计。你他妈的 又起来了。还没开始呢。
This ain't starting, man. You fucked up again. It ain't starting.
我要踢你的 屁股，踢你的屁股。
I'm gonna kick your ass, kick your ass.
快点，现在。来吧， 所有人，这不是开始。
Come on, now. Come on, everybody, this ain't starting.
来吧，混蛋， 修理那该死的车。
Come on, motherfucker, fix the fucking car.
来吧。你搞砸了 再说一遍，你这个混蛋。
Come on. You fucked up again, you asshole.
你在上面干什么，文尼？
What you doing up there, Vinnie?
喔！好吧。 我们走了。走吧！
Whoo! All right. And we're off. Let's go!
死吧！
Die!
-死吧！ -汤米！
- Die! - Tommy!
死吧！
Die!
汤米！
Tommy!
死吧！死吧！
Die! Die!
死吧！死吧！死吧！
Die! Die! Die!
汤米！
Tommy!
死吧！
Die!
-汤米！ -死吧！
- Tommy! - Die!
死吧！
Die!
死吧！死吧！死吧！
Die! Die! Die!
给你。
There you go.
-爷爷。 -怎么了，儿子？
- Gramps. - What is it, son?
我能去看我哥哥吗？ 他明天会在城里。
Can I go see my brother? He'll be in town tomorrow.
我们拭目以待。你知道怎么做 我感觉到了。
We'll see. You know how I feel about that.
-但是，爷爷。。。 -我说，我们拭目以待，雷吉。
- But, Gramps... - I said, we'll see, Reggie.
嘿。
Hey.
过来，鲁莽的雷吉。
Come here, Reggie the Reckless.
帮我一个忙。别吻我 周围有人，好吗？
Do me a favor. Don't kiss me when there's people around, okay?
哦。好吧，很酷。继续让 其他人都知道早餐准备好了。
Oh. Okay, it's cool. Go on and let everyone else know breakfast is ready.
喂，早餐！过来拿！
Yo, breakfast! Come and get it!
我本可以这么做的。
I could've done that.
一、乔伊小姐已经来了。
I, uh, miss Joey already.
我也是。
So do I.
我希望维克多 他怎么了。
I hope Victor gets what's coming to him.
-早上好，各位。 -早上好。
- Morning, everybody. - Morning.
-维奥莱特，你放的地方太多了。 -嗯？
- Violet, you set too many places. - Huh?
我说，你放的地方太多了。
I said, you set too many places.
-不，我没有。 -是的，你做到了。
- No, I didn't. - Yes, you did.
别以为维克多和乔伊会 今天早上和我们一起，维奥莱特。
Don't think Victor and Joey will be joining us this morning, Violet.
嘿，或者其他任何一个早晨。
Heh, or any other morning.
-雷吉！ -哦，天哪。我很抱歉。
- Reggie! - Oh, God. I'm sorry.
你没有安排好地方 为了一个死人。
You don't set a place for a dead person.
-我说了对不起！ -怎么回事？
- I said I was sorry! - What's going on here?
听着，我知道你们的感受。
Look, I know how you all feel.
这东西不是 对我们任何人来说都很容易。
This thing is not easy for any of us.
我们就吃早饭吧。
So let's just have breakfast.
我很抱歉，维。我太过分了。
I'm sorry, Vi. I was out of line.
-埃迪呢？ -他在楼上。
- Where's Eddie? - He's upstairs.
汤米，你介意告诉我吗 埃迪下楼？
Tommy, would you mind telling Eddie to come downstairs?
汤米？你介意吗？
Tommy? Would you mind?
是的，好吧。
Yeah, all right.
混蛋。
Asshole.
放松点，长官。什么 错了，没有幽默感？
Relax, chief. What's wrong, no sense of humor?
你不能开个玩笑吗？
Can't you take a joke?
放松点。放松点。没关系。 没关系。不会有事的。
Just relax. Just relax. It's all right. It's all right. It's gonna be all right.
放松点。是啊。 会没事的。
Just relax. Yeah. It's gonna be just fine.
我要把你切成小块 小碎片，我的朋友。
I'm gonna chop you into itty-bitty little pieces, my friend.
就像他们对猪做的那样 在那该死的疯狂农场，嘿。
Just like they done to that piggo over there at that fucking crazy farm, heh.
哎呀！
Ee-yah!
你这个大假阴茎。 他妈的吃你的泔水。
You big dildo. Eat your fucking slop.
我不是他妈的做得最好吗 全世界都在炖？
Ain't I make the best goddamn stew in the whole wide world?
最好的炖肉 全世界，妈妈。
Best goddamn stew in the whole wide world, Mama.
是那个该死的狼， 会再杀了我的人。
It's that goddamn coyote, gonna try to kill my lot again.
我要给那个混蛋看一次 对所有人来说。听到了吗，小家伙？
I'm gonna show that bastard once and for all. You hear me, Junior?
天啊！你他妈是谁 你他妈的想要什么？
Holy shit! Who the fuck are you and what the fuck do you want?
女士，我两天没吃东西了。 我想挣一顿饭。
Ma'am, I ain't eaten in two days. I'd like to earn a meal.
-是吗？你是做什么的？ -不管你需要做什么。
- Yeah? What do you do? - Whatever you need done.
可以。清理所有的垃圾 从鸡窝里出来。。。
Okay. Clean all the shit out of the chicken coop...
把它扔到棚子后面。
and dump it behind the shed.
当你得到所有的 去你妈的，我来填饱你的肚子。
You come back here when you got all the shit out and then I'll fill your stomach.
是的，女士。
Yes, ma'am.
真他妈的丑 去那里的人。
That is one fucking ugly man that goes there.
-那是个他妈的丑男人，妈妈。 -你能关上你的陷阱吗？
- That's one fucking ugly man, Mama. - Would you shut your trap?
你知道，你不是这样的 你知道，漂亮的你自己。
You know, you ain't so pretty yourself, you know.
我自己也不漂亮，我知道。
I ain't so pretty myself, I know.
嗨，耶！
Hi-yah!
我要这一切 区域彻底梳理。
I want every inch of this area combed thoroughly.
把你找到的东西带回来。 什么都行。开始吧。
Bring back anything you find. Anything. Get going.
是的，先生。
Yes, sir.
怎么回事？
What the hell's going on here?
你在跟我说话吗，警长？
You talking to me, sheriff?
-嗯？ -哦。
- Huh? - Oh.
我以为你在跟我说话。
I thought you was talking to me.
不，罗伊。没关系。前进。 把他们弄出去。
No, Roy. It's okay. Go ahead. Get them out of here.
看来我们有个疯子 逍遥法外，嗯，警长？
Looks like we got us a maniac on the loose, huh, sheriff?
拉娜！嘿，拉娜！
Lana! Hey, Lana!
对不起，巴斯特。我们关门了。嘿。
Sorry, buster. We're closed. Heh.
没关系。我只是 想要外卖订单。
That's all right. I just want a takeout order.
-是的，嗯？ -是的。
- You do, huh? - Yeah.
好吧，你想要什么？
Well, what would you like?
我想让拉娜走， 她身上什么都没有。
I would like Lana, to go, with nothing on her.
哦？谁想要她？
Oh? And who wants her?
昂格人的骄傲 心理健康研究所。。。
The pride of the Unger Institute of Mental Health...
他刚刚扔掉了最后一个便盆 很想参加聚会。
who has just dumped his last bedpan and would like very much to party.
你能出去吗？
Will you get your ass out here?
拉娜？嗯，我不知道 关于这个。我得问问她。
Lana? Hmm, I don't know about that. I'll have to ask her.
嘿，拉娜。你想要的 比利？你确定？
Hey, Lana. You want Billy? You sure?
她说她也想要你。
She says she wants you too.
但你得等一会儿 几分钟后她就可以进去了。
But you have to wait a few minutes till she's done inside.
雅虎！
Yahoo!
在那里。我要去参加聚会。
There. I'm going to party.
现在是表演时间。哈，哈。
It's showtime. Ha, ha.
就这样。
That's it.
就这样。就这样 他妈的就在那儿。
That's it. That's the whole fucking thing right there.
就在这里。你只是 呆在那儿，娃娃。
There it is. You just stay right there, doll.
这就是 医生命令道。
That's just what the doctor ordered.
一点也不像 预防医学。
Nothing like a little preventive medicine.
天气预报是多云的 在山上。。。
And the forecast is cloudy in the mountains...
山谷里阳光明媚 你鼻子上起了雪。
sunny in the valleys and snow flurries up your nose.
嗯。
Mm.
我不知道他是否爱我
I don't know if he loves me
但我认为他是
But I think he does
比利？
Billy?
女孩，你真性感。
Girl, you are so hot.
嘿，拉娜！
Hey, Lana!
她在干什么？
What the fuck is she doing?
嘿！
Hey!
天哪！来吧，好吗？
Jesus Christ! Come on, will you?
拉娜！
Lana!
嘿！嘿！
Hey! Hey!
你这只坏猫。你这只坏猫。那个 不太好。我不再喜欢你了。
You bad kitty. You bad kitty. That isn't nice. I don't like you anymore.
你这个坏猫咪。我喂你，我爱 你和你那样吓唬我。
You bad kitty. I feed you, I love you and you scare me like that.
去吧，凯蒂。
Go on, kitty.
对不起，嘿。
Sorry, heh.
比利？
Billy?
比利，你是什么 做什么？天很冷。
Billy, what are you doing? It's cold.
这很可爱。我喜欢这个。 很多。
This is cute. I like this. A whole lot.
你会浪费很多 这样的钱，聪明的。
You're gonna waste a lot of money this way, smarty.
哦，好吧，只是 对我来说意味着更多。
Oh, well, that just means more for me.
哦。
Oh.
嗯，好吃。
Mm, yummy.
哦，天哪。比利？比利！
Oh, my God. Billy? Billy!
我不在乎你是否必须 你妈的在监狱里！
I don't care if you have to put your fucking mother behind bars!
给我那个该死的疯子 对这场混乱负责。
Get me the goddamn psycho who's responsible for this mess.
我是说，该死，塔克，什么 这到底是怎么回事？
I mean, shit, Tucker, what the hell's going on here?
我是说，这是个小镇，伙计。
I mean, this is a small town, man.
小城镇 应该是安全的。
And small towns are supposed to be safe.
我知道是谁。
I know who it is.
-什么？ -我说，我知道是谁。
- What? - I said, I know who it is.
-谁？ -我是杰森?沃赫斯。
- Who? - It's Jason Voorhees.
杰森?沃里斯？
Jason Voorhees?
你他妈的疯了！ 你在外面晒太阳太久了。
You're out of your fucking mind! You've been out in the sun too long.
杰森?沃里斯死了！
Jason Voorhees is dead!
他的尸体被火化了。他是 只有一把灰。
His body was cremated. He's nothing but a handful of ash.
你肯定知道，市长？
You know that for sure, mayor?
你在吗？ 你看到他火化了吗？
Were you there? Did you see him cremated?
-杰森?沃里斯。 -是的。
- Jason Voorhees. - Yes.
我真不敢相信！
I can't believe this!
在这里。这是你的 杰森?沃希斯来了。
Here. This is your Jason Voorhees here.
这个。
This.
你的屁股在这排队， 塔克。你明白了吗？
Your ass is on the line here, Tucker. Are you getting that?
你给我找个活生生的嫌疑犯。
You get me a goddamn live suspect.
-你他妈的！你真的吓到我了。 -你喜欢它。
- You fuck! You really scared me. - You loved it.
-你想要更多？ -埃迪，我们不能。
- You want more? - Eddie, we can't.
-马特会杀了我们。 -去他妈的。
- Matt'll kill us. - Fuck him.
-去你妈的。 -没错。操我。
- Fuck you. - Exactly. Fuck me.
快点，蒂娜。
Come on, Tina.
来吧。来吧。
Come on. Come on.
来吧。
Come on.
小心泥土。小心泥土。
Watch the dirt. Watch the dirt.
-什么？ -等等。等一下。
- What? - Wait. Wait a minute.
尤其是在这个场合。
Especially for the occasion.
-我得去洗个澡。 -好吧，甜心。
- I gotta go wash up. - Okay, sugar.
-快回来。 -我在赶时间。
- Hurry back. - I'm hurrying.
我回来了。
I'm back.
这是什么？睡觉？嘿。
What is this? Sleeping? Hey.
让我们把这个节目搬上路吧！
Let's get this show on the road!
等等，雷吉，我来了。
Wait a minute, Reggie, I'm coming.
我只是不明白。
I just don't understand it.
现在，雷吉，我要你 和帕姆做个好孩子。
Now, Reggie, I want you to be a good kid with Pam.
-她帮了我们两个大忙。 -是的，如果她来过这里。
- She's doing us both a great favor. - Yeah, if she ever gets here.
别进去了 恶魔的麻烦，你听到了吗？
And don't go getting in any trouble with Demon, you hear?
好吧，好吧。 喂，帕姆，快点！
All right, all right. Yo, Pam, come on!
蒂娜和埃迪会出现的 一旦他们饿了。。。
Tina and Eddie are gonna show up the minute they get hungry...
所以别担心了。
so stop worrying.
我不再担心了， 我只是生气了。
I'm not worried anymore, I'm just pissed.
好吧，住手。
Well, stop it.
听着，你为什么不 带汤米一起去？
Look, why don't you take Tommy with you?
可能对他有好处 他离开这里一会儿。
Probably do him good to get him out of here for a while.
是的，这是个好主意。
Yeah, that's a good idea.
汤米？帕姆要带走雷吉 今晚去看他哥哥。
Tommy? Pam's taking Reggie to see his brother tonight.
-你为什么不跟他们一起去？ -是啊，好主意。现在，我们走。
- Why don't you ride along with them? - Yeah, great idea. Now, let's go.
你为什么不去看看 你能做什么，嗯？
Why don't you go see what you can do, huh?
可以。
Okay.
汤米。
Tommy.
来吧。会很有趣的。
Come on. It'll be fun.
可以？
Okay?
很好。
Good.
-来吧。 -不，我在这儿等。
- Come on. - No. I'll wait here.
-来吧。 -我没事。
- Come on. - I'm okay.
哟，恶魔！
Yo, Demon!
大灰狼 敲我的门？
That the big bad wolf rapping at my door?
是的，兄弟，是我， 是我。开门！
Yeah, bro, it's me, it's me. Open up!
-是你，鲁莽？ -开门！
- That you, Reckless? - Open up the door!
哦，天哪。好吧，去 你这混蛋，小子！
Oh, my God. Well, get your ass in here, boy!
天啊，很高兴见到你，伙计。 该死，你看起来不错！
God, it's good to see you, dude. Damn, you look good!
我知道，我知道。嘿。
I know, I know. Heh.
哦，天哪。看看这个。上帝啊。 嘿，你吃过饭吗？
Oh, God. Look at this. God. Hey, you had any dinner?
在这里。吃一片玉米片。伙计。
Here. Have an enchilada. Man.
哇，伙计，你从哪儿弄来的 那些坏戒指？
Wow, man, where'd you get those bad rings from?
如果你在世界各地 你哥哥有，你有东西。
If you been around the world as long as your big brother have, you get things.
吓死人了！你从哪儿弄来的？
Freaking-A! Where'd you get that?
嘿，冷静点，伙计。嘿，说 你好，安妮塔。她是我女朋友。
Hey, calm down, dude. Hey, say hello to Anita. She's my girlfriend.
你好，美女。
Hello, beautiful.
嘿，小弟弟。 怎么了？嘿。
Hey, little brother. What's happening? Heh.
听着，我要你们 去见某人。
Listen, I want you all to meet somebody.
嘿，帕姆。哟，帕姆，过来 过来，宝贝，过来。
Hey, Pam. Yo, Pam, come here, baby, come here.
-这是我的朋友，帕姆。 -嗨。
- This is my friend, Pam. - Hi.
她是我女朋友。
She's my girlfriend.
怎么了，帕姆？
What's up, Pam?
-帕姆，你饿了吗？ -哦，不，谢谢。
- Pam, you hungry? - Oh, no, thanks.
你要玉米卷吗？蛋卷？ 一片披萨怎么样？
You want a taco? Egg roll? What about a slice of pizza?
-不，谢谢。 -奶酪和香肠。
- No, thank you. - Cheese and sausage.
你呢，兄弟？ 我知道你想要什么。
What about you, brother? I know what you want.
-要啤酒吗？ -是的，我要。。。
- Want a beer? - Yeah, I'll take...
-离开这里。 -嘿。
- Get out of here. - Heh.
我来告诉你。为什么？ 你不拿这个吗？
I'll tell you what. Why don't you take this?
真的。
Wow.
嘿，伙计，真糟糕！
Hey, man, this is bad!
什么都不好 为了我弟弟。
Nothing is too good for my little brother.
你也要给我这个？
You gonna give me this too?
我抓到你了，不是吗？真的？ 吓到你了，不是吗？
I got you, didn't I? Really scared you, didn't I?
你是哑巴还是什么？
Are you dumb or something?
你这个疯子！
You a crazy from the loony bin!
哦，我妈妈要把你剁了 变成小碎片，我的朋友！
Oh, my mama's gonna chop you up into itty-bitty pieces, my friend!
听到了吗？我说， 你听到了吗？
You hear me? I said, are you hearing me?
我说，你听见了吗？
I said, are you hearing me?
你这个该死的疯子！
You fucking lunatic!
汤米！
Tommy!
雷吉，我们得走了。
Reggie, we've gotta go now.
-没事的，兄弟。保重，好吗？ -谢谢你的晚餐。
- It's okay, bro. Take care, all right? - Thanks for the dinner.
-任何时候。 -保持冷静，宝贝。
- Anytime. - Stay cool, baby.
-嘿，保持安全，鲁莽。 -我会的。
- Hey, stay safe, Reckless. - I will.
-你知道，我已经想他了。 -是啊，他真可爱。
- You know, I miss him already. - Yeah, he's a cutie-pie.
-想打这个吗？ -是的。
- Wanna hit this? - Yeah.
发生了什么？
What's wrong?
-嘿，你还好吧？ -哦。是那些该死的炸玉米饼。
- Hey, you okay? - Ooh. It's them damn enchiladas.
你会没事吧？
You gonna be all right?
那是谁？
Who's that?
住手！
Stop it!
你会明白的，婊子！
You gonna get it, bitch!
哦，放松点，恶魔。你会感觉到 在你大便之后好多了。嘿。
Oh, lighten up, Demon. You'll feel a lot better after you shit. Heh.
我出去的时候会感觉好多了 在这里。这个垃圾箱真恶心！
I'll feel a lot better when I'm out of here. This shit box is gross!
你最好小心那条蛇 会爬上那个垃圾桶。。。
You better watch out for the snake that's gonna crawl up that crapper...
咬你的屁股，呵呵。
and bite your ass, heh.
哦，宝贝
Ooh, baby
嘿，宝贝
Hey, baby
哦，宝贝
Ooh, baby
哦，宝贝，哦，宝贝
Ooh, baby, ooh, baby
嘿，宝贝
Hey, baby
哦，宝贝，哦，宝贝
Ooh, baby, ooh, baby
哦，宝贝，哦…
Ooh, baby, ooh...
安妮塔？嘿，女孩，怎么了？
Anita? Hey, girl, what's up?
嘿！
Hey!
可以。我告诉过你这不好笑。
Okay. I told you this isn't funny.
现在你会明白的，婊子。
Now you gonna get it, bitch.
安妮塔！
Anita!
马特走了。乔治也是。
Matt's gone. George too.
-你确定吗？ -我到处找。
- Are you sure? - I looked everywhere.
蒂娜和埃迪还没有 也回来吧。
And Tina and Eddie haven't come back either.
-他们在哪里？ -听着，没关系。冷静点，杰克。
- Where are they? - Look, it's okay. Calm down, Jake.
让我们慢慢来。 马特说他要去哪里？
Let's try to take this slowly. Where did Matt say he was going?
-他没有。 -是的，他有。
- He didn't. - Yes, he did.
他说他要去 找蒂娜和埃迪。
He said he was gonna go look for Tina and Eddie.
汤米在哪里？我想 他和你在一起。
Where's Tommy? I thought he was with you.
-爷爷呢？ -我不知道，雷吉。
- And where's Gramps? - I don't know, Reggie.
你们为什么不都进去？ 我要去找所有人。
Look, why don't you all go inside? I'm gonna go find everyone.
-杰克，我让你负责。 -是的。
- Jake, I'm putting you in charge. - Yes.
而你，有点鲁莽， 我要你在床上睡觉。。。
And you, little Reckless, I want you in bed asleep...
等我回来，对吧？
by the time I get back, right?
没问题。
No problem.
可以。
Okay.
我给你做晚饭，小朋友！ 听到了吗，伙计？
I'm making your dinner, Junior! You hearing me, fella?
他伤害了我，妈！你…吗 听到了吗？他们伤害了我！
He hurt me, Ma! Do you hear me? They hurt me!
我给你做晚饭！
I am making your dinner!
他们伤害了我，妈！ 你会杀了他们吗？
They hurt me, Ma! Will you murder them?
把他们砍了杀了 他们！听到了吗？
Chop them and kill them! You hear me?
你在听我说话吗，孩子？ 从那该死的自行车上下来。。。
Are you hearing me, boy? Get off that fucking bike...
过来吃我的炖肉！
and come here and eat my stew!
时间到了，你这个混蛋。
About time, you fuckwad.
知道你不能 不要吃我的炖肉。
Knew you couldn't pass up on my stew.
你听见了吗，小家伙？ 你说话。你这个笨蛋？
You hearing me, Junior? You talk. You dumb?
这里太寂寞了。
It's so lonely here.
好像只有我们两个 全世界的人都离开了。
Like we were the only two people left in the whole world.
也许我们是。
Maybe we are.
也许当我们回到岸边， 其他人都会消失。
Maybe when we get back to shore, everybody else will have disappeared.
我喜欢。你不会吗？
I 'd like that. Wouldn't you?
罗宾。啊哼。
Robin. Ahem.
我们差不多到过这里 八个月了，对吧？
We've been here nearly eight months now, right?
啊哈。
Uh-huh.
很长时间才知道 有人，你不觉得吗？
That's a long time to get to know somebody, don't you think?
嘘。
Shh.
-杰克，求你了。 -当然，当然。
- Jake, please. - Sure, sure.
我们可以去任何我们想去的地方…
We could go anywhere we wanted...
我们可以住在 世界上最大的房子。
and we could live in the biggest house in the world.
只是，我想住在一所小房子里。 刚好够我们两个人用。
Only, I 'd like to live in a little house. Just big enough for the two of us.
只是，会有更多 比我们两个，不是吗？
Only, there's gonna be more than two of us, isn't there?
我喜欢你，罗宾。
I like you, Robin.
-很多。 -我也喜欢你，杰克。
- A lot. - And I like you too, Jake.
你知道吗？很多？
You do? A lot?
你在说什么，杰克？
What are you talking about, Jake?
休斯敦大学。。。
Uh...
我想和你在一起。
I wanna be with you.
我真的很想和你在一起。
I really do wanna be with you.
我想和你做爱。
I wanna make love with you.
-我不能。。。 -我不是故意的。
- I can't... - I didn't mean it.
我不是故意的。
I didn't mean it.
我说，我。。。我不是故意的！
I said, I... I didn't mean it!
不及物动词？
Vi?
不及物动词！
Vi!
-我想和你谈谈。 -嗯？
- Vi, I'd like to talk to you. - Huh?
-我要和你谈谈。 -能等一下吗？
- I need to talk to you. - Can it wait?
不。
No.
雷吉。雷吉？来吧。 雷吉，醒醒。
Reggie. Reggie? Come on. Reggie, wake up.
-嗯。 -快点，该睡觉了。
- Mm. - Come on, it's time to go to bed.
雷吉，醒醒。雷吉！
Reggie, wake up. Reggie!
好吧，按你的方式。
Okay, your way.
杰克，对不起。
Jake, I'm sorry.
你知道，有时候，罗宾， 你真蠢。
You know, sometimes, Robin, you are just so stupid.
有个这么冷的人 他眼中没有生命
There was a man so cold No life was in his eyes
他看了那么一眼 我从没见过他笑过
He had a look so hard I 'd never seen him smile
那我早该告诉你的 你以前都听过
I could've told you then You'd heard it all before
现在你还悬而未决 您必须等待更多信息
And now you're in suspense You have to wait for more
在所有这些神秘中 你被吓到了
In all those mysteries You're taken by surprise
你从没想过会看到 他的眼神
You never thought to see That look was in his eyes
有个男人 他眼中没有生命
There's a man with no life in his eyes
他们现在在干什么？
What are them nuts up to now?
哟，汤米。你回来了？ 汤米，你在这里？
Yo, Tommy. You back? Tommy, you in here?
哟，汤米。
Yo, Tommy.
怎么了，雷吉？我是帕姆。什么 怎么了？怎么了
What is it, Reggie? It's Pam. What's the matter? What's the matter?
-是我。它是什么？这是怎么一回事？ -在汤米的房间里。
- It's me. What is it? What is it? - In Tommy's room.
可以。好吧。你留在这里。 放松点。我马上回来。可以？
Okay. All right. You stay here. Relax. I'll be right back. Okay?
快走！
Move!
-啊！ -起来！起床！
- Aah! - Get up! Get up!
倒霉！
Shit!
快跑！快点！走吧！
Run! Come on! Let's go!
帮帮我们！
Help us!
雷吉！雷吉！
Reggie! Reggie!
帕姆，你在哪儿？
Pam, where are you?
-帕姆！ -雷吉！
- Pam! - Reggie!
雷吉！
Reggie!
雷吉！雷吉！
Reggie! Reggie!
雷吉。
Reggie.
不！不！
No! No!
不！
No!
哦，没关系，雷吉。 没关系。没关系。
Oh, it's okay, Reggie. It's okay. It's okay.
上帝啊。
God.
哦，上帝。
Oh, God.
是啊！好吧，帕姆！
Yeah! All right, Pam!
是啊！
Yeah!
汤米！汤米！
Tommy! Tommy!
快跑，汤米，快跑！
Run, Tommy, run!
快跑！他会杀了你！
Run! He'll kill you!
-杰森？ -听我说！
- Jason? - Listen to me!
快跑！快走！汤米，出去！
Run! Go! Tommy, get out!
-杰森？ -出去！
- Jason? - Get out!
-记住。 -听着！哦，汤米，走！
- Remember. - Listen! Oh, Tommy, go!
拜托，汤米！
Please, Tommy!
-汤米！ -记住。
- Tommy! - Remember.
不要。
Don't.
-记住。 -死吧！
- Remember. - Die!
-杰森。  -记住，记住。
- Jason. - Remember, remember.
-记住，记住，记住… -汤米！汤米！
- Remember, remember, remember... - Tommy! Tommy!
在这里，汤米！快点！在这里！
Up here, Tommy! Come on! Up here!
快点！来吧。
Come on! Come on.
-汤米，求你了！ -快点，汤米，上来！
- Tommy, please! - Come on, Tommy, up here!
-快点！ -快点，快点！
- Come on! - Come on, hurry up!
汤米，快点！
Tommy, hurry up!
快点，快点。
Come on, come on.
来吧，汤米，你可以 做吧！快点，汤米！
Come on, Tommy, you can do it! Come on, Tommy!
-汤米，求你了！ -汤米，快点！
- Tommy, please! - Tommy, hurry up!
握住我的手。抓住我的手！
Take my hand. Take my hand!
来吧，是的。
Come on, yeah.
-来吧，是的。 -再来一杯，汤米。来吧。
- Come on, yeah. - Just one more, Tommy. Come on.
快点，你能行的！
Come on, you can do it!
不！
No!
帕姆！不！请帮帮我！
Pam! No! Please help me!
拜托！拜托，有人 帮助我！帕姆！
Please! Please, somebody help me! Pam!
救命啊！救命啊！
Help! Help!
救命啊！救命啊！求求你，救命！
Help! Help! Please, help!
你好吗？
How are you doing?
真是个孩子。
Quite a kid.
我们在罗伊身上找到的。
We found this on Roy.
被砍死的孩子 在木桩旁是罗伊的儿子。
The kid who was axed to death at the woodpile was Roy's son.
天知道罗伊为什么留着它 隐藏了这么多年，但他做到了。
God only knows why Roy kept it hidden all these years, but he did.
罗伊真的很孤独。
Roy was a real loner.
从不多说话，甚至 给其他医护人员。
Never talked much, not even to the other paramedics.
我猜他是什么时候 打电话到现场。。。
I guess when he was called to the scene...
他看到那是他自己的 乔伊，都被砍成碎片。。。
and he saw that it was his own Joey, all hacked to pieces...
哦，天哪。
Oh, God.
我们也发现了这些。
We also found these.
我猜他用了杰森的东西。。。
I guess he used the Jason thing...
掩盖。
to cover up with.
汤米。
Tommy.
你好。
Hi.
哦，天哪。
Oh, my God.